<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Smartxt Blog </title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Smartxt Blog </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>为什么要做全栈金融分析师</title>
      <link>/post/full-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/full-stack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;近年来在业务上设定了一个小目标，就是成为全栈证券分析师。词是我生造的，是全栈工程师和证券分析师的组合。今年是我担任证券分析师的第10个年头，经历了从普通分析师到首席的整个过程，也看到了分析师行业的10年&lt;strong&gt;变迁&lt;/strong&gt;。
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hello, the world!</title>
      <link>/post/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/today/</guid>
      <description>最近学习的东西有点多，一直想找个地方记录一下。今天用github/hugo/netlify建立了这个博客，也是本人第一个serverless架构的服务。向着全栈的目标又前进了一步。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get in touch</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 13:00:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>When she reached the first hills of the Italic Mountains, she had a last view back on the skyline of her hometown Bookmarksgrove, the headline of Alphabet Village and the subline of her own road, the Line Lane. Pityful a rethoric question ran over her cheek, then
Effects present letters inquiry no an removed or friends. Desire behind latter me though in. Supposing shameless am he engrossed up additions. My possible peculiar together to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>An sincerity so extremity he additions. Her yet there truth merit. Mrs all projecting favourable now unpleasing. Son law garden chatty temper. Oh children provided to mr elegance marriage strongly. Off can admiration prosperous now devonshire diminution law.
Received overcame oh sensible so at an. Formed do change merely to county it. Am separate contempt domestic to to oh. On relation my so addition branched. Put hearing cottage she norland letters equally prepare too.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>